Shikha Choubey (1) Featured

UI Developer seeking roles in Software Development, UI Development, Website Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Unit Testing, Angular, JavaScript, jQuery, RxJs, Azure, HTML, CSS, JSON



Current Designation: UI Developer Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Interwork Software Solutions Private Limited Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Noida Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electronics/Telecommunication] Pref. Location: Noida, Delhi

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: UI Developer, Software Developer, Software Development, UI Development, Website Development, Application

Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Unit

Testing, Angular, JavaScript, jQuery, RxJs, Azure, HTML, CSS, JSON

Email - id Verified: Phone Number |

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Summary

A competent professional with nearly 4 years of rich & extensive experience in UI Designing cum Developing Proven success in developing user centered design (UCD) process flows, wireframes, mockups and all graphic components and digital prototypes and visual design for web and marketing interfaces

Experience in front-end development of web applications from requirement analysis to system study, designing, coding, testing, documentation and implementation

Impressive fast track career driven by challenges and desire to be successful, with an expertise in leading multiple projects Lead a diverse group of individuals working on a project, ensuring not only that the project is completed, but that the project staff is able to work as a cohesive team

Expertise in solid writing background to produce quality project documentation

Work Experience

Interwork Software Solutions Private Limited as UI Developer May 2019 to Till Date

Frontend developer with converting wireframe and integrated interface with manual testing

Stucorner Solutions as Software Engineer Oct 2018 to Apr 2019

Webcontentor India Private Limited as Software Engineer Jun 2016 to Apr 2018

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Rajiv Gandhi Proudyogiki Vishwavidyalaya (RGPV), Bhopal in 2014

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
WINDOWS 7, WINDOWS 8	
Angular JS, Angular 2	
TypeScript	
BOOTSTRAP	
HTML, CSS, JSON	
Eclipse, Sublime Text Editor	
VISUAL STUDIO	
GitHub	
JavaScript	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time